# **NOMAN AFZAL**

# 3D Artist

+923083833433

Islamabad, Pakistan

Bē https://www.behance.net/nomanafzal\_fbx



#### **EDUCATION**

12/09/2017 - 14/10/2021

#### **BS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

Bahria University Islamabad, Pakistan

## **SKILLS**

**PROFESSIONAL** 

**Technical Proficiency** 

Creativity

**Problem Solving** 

# **TOOLS & TECHNIQUES**

3D Modeling Material Maps

Interior Designing Rigging
Environment Designing Lightning
Product Showcase Animation
Assets Modeling Rendering

Texturing UV Mapping

Concept Art Interpretation NFTs

Game Maps and Environment Creation

Blender Raptor-Ultra

Rigify, Auto-Rig, Facelt Buildify

Adobe Substance Painter Adobe After Effects
Adobe Illustrator Adobe Phototshop

Design review Isometric

Technical requirments styling Computer Generated Imagery UV

Low Poly Models 3D Graphics

#### **HOBBIES**

Badminton
 Cricket
 Hiking

#### **PROFILE**

Highly skilled 3D artist specializing in 3D modeling, texturing, animation, and rendering. Two years of hands-on experience creating captivating 3D models and environments. Demonstrate proficiency in Blender, Adobe Substance Painter, Adobe Photoshop, and Adobe After Effects.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## 3D ARTIST

Pixeltech.CO | 01/2022 - CURRENT

- Modeling and Texturing 3D assets.
- Demonstrated proficiency in 3D modeling, character rigging, texturing, animation, rendering, product visualization, environment designing, interior designing, and animation.
- Experienced in the creation and minting of NFTs.
- Experienced industry-standard software, such as Blender, Substance Painter, Adobe Photoshop, and Adobe After Effects.
- Consistently delivered high-quality results on time, showcasing strong attention to detail and the ability to project requirements.

## INTERNEE

CYBER RECONNAISSANCE | 01/2020 - 05/2020 AND COMBAT (CRC) LAB

- Website Development using Reactjs, NodeJS, ExpressJS.
- Designed Frontend of an admin panel
- · Worked on Malware Detection System.
- Wrote python scripts in linux platform to receive the logs from different machines.

## LANGUAGES

- English Professional
- Urdu/Hindi Native